Thomas Loch

Thomas_Loch@hotmail.com | (+31)6 00 00 00 00 Vught, Noord Brabant

Summary

Experienced Technical assistant with a demonstrated ability of working in the electrical and electronic manufacturing industry. Skilled in Autodesk Inventor, AutoCAD, Altium Designer. Strong professional with a Bachelor of Aviation from Griffith University. Currently studying a Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) Majoring in Computer Systems at USQ.

Education

2018 - 2021, University of Southern Queensland, Australia

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) Majoring in Computer Systems GPA: 6.25

2009 - 2012, Griffith University, Australia

Bachelor of Aviation, Graduate Diploma of Flight Management GPA: 4.6

2007 - 2008, Metropoltan South Institute of TAFE

Certificate III in Computer Aided Drafting

2004 - 2008, Loganlea State High School

High School Certificate Year 12

Work Experience

07/2016 - 11/2017, Pacific Data Systems Australia Pty. Ltd.

Production Technician | R&D Technician

- Assembly and testing of company products, using machines and hand tools.
- Assembly of pcb's, using a pick and place machine (Autotronik BA385V2), and reflow oven.
- Assembly of small R&D pcb batches, using hand tools, down to 0402 sized components.
- Programming, fault finding and fixing of assembly and R&D pcb's.
- Designing circuit boards, to a strict set of design standards based on product needs.
- Maintaining an up to date inventory of all components, and upkeeping the BOM of all company electronic products.
- Making inhouse modbus testing software using C#

11/2013 - 07/2016, Aldi

Trainee Store Manager (from 10/2014) | Workplace Health & Safety Officer

- Exceptional customer service.
- Responsibility of all store money.
- Ensuring shifts happen as scheduled, within operational guidelines at all times.
- Staff training, and maintenance of standards among all staff.

04/2011 - 07/2013, Woolworths Supermarket

Perishables Assistant | Storeman

- Customer service.
- Stock monitoring, presentation, and preparation.
- Cold stock handling.
- Oversight of safety on the dock.
- Accepting deliveries & safe loading/unloading of trucks.

05/2009 - 10/2010, IKEA Logan

Self Serve Co-Worker

- Customer service.
- Assisting customer with heavy lifting.
- Warehouse tidyness & preperation.
- Stock handling.

Skills

Languages

- English
- Dutch

Computer software | languages

- AutoCAD 2d/DXF preperation for production.
- o Inventor 3d modeling and sheet metal design.
- Altium 2-4 layer design, down to 0402 size
- C/C++ Custom keyboards, usb io boards
- C# Testing software, using RS485/Modbus
- HTML/JavaScript Basic website design, pure JavaScript
- Latex Math assesment, resumes & cover letters
- Git multi user project (pcb design projects)

Other

I run my own business designing and selling custom keyboards

Aviation

License

Commercial Pilot License 11/04/2012 | Training Completed at the Airline Academy of Australia Private Pilot License 18/07/2011 | Training Completed at the Airline Academy of Australia

Rating & Endorsements

- Single Engine (<5,700 kg)
- Beechcraft Duchess BE76
- Manual Propeller Pitch Control
- Retractable Undercarriage
- Tailwheel Undercarriage

Flight Hours

0	Total time:	240 Hrs
0	Pilot in Command:	80 Hrs
0	Multi Engine:	30 Hrs
0	Night Time:	12 Hrs
0	Beechcraft Duchess:	30 Hrs
0	Cessna 172RG:	49 Hrs
0	Cessna 172R/S:	154 Hrs
0	Citabria:	7 Hrs

References

Martin Akman

Software Engineer, Pacific Data Systems Australia Pty. Ltd. +61 7 3361 2000 | makman@pacdatasys.com.au

David Hugman

Production Manager, Pacific Data Systems Australia Pty. Ltd. +61 7 3361 2000 | dhugman@pacdatasys.com.au

Mark Fergusson

R&D Manager, Pacific Data Systems Australia Pty. Ltd. +61 7 3361 2000 | mfergusson@pacdatasys.com.au